wishscope.com 2012-12-26

# WishScope

### Introduction

This personal information protection policy (hereinafter referred to as "Private Policy") is to explain how Zawatt Inc. (hereinafter referred to as "this company") handles a user's personal information.This company collects/uses/shares/ privacy information (as defined below) in accordance with the terms and conditions specified below to operate the service, "WishScope," which has functions such as posting/applying for/approving/ messaging personal advertisements (hereinafter referred to as "this service") and keeps such information under a strict security and confidentiality standard.

### Definition of Privacy Information

The "personal information" included within the privacy information refers to "personal information" under the Private Information Protection Law, which is the information concerning a natural person, referring to the name, date of birth, address, telephone number, contact information and any other description included in said information which enables the specific individual to be identified.

The "history information and characteristic information" included within the privacy information refers to information other than the "personal information” specified above, such as the services the users used, merchandise purchased, a history of the browsed pages and advertisements, search key words that the user searched, the time zone of the usage, the method of the use, the use environment, the user's IP address, cookie information, location information, and terminal identification information.

### About the Purpose of the Use of the Personal Information

This company will use the user's personal information for the following purposes:

  1. To provide information for this service and information related to this service.
  2. To confirm a user's identity and for authentication purposes in settlement of accounts.
  3. To improve the safety of the transactions between users such as to resolve disputes, fee collection issues and other issues.
  4. To notify users of necessary matters to operate this service (including notification via e-mail).
  5. To transmit e-mail magazines that this service thinks may be useful for the users.
  6. To analyze necessary data for the development of new features to this service in a format where the individual users cannot be identified.
  7. To distribute targeted advertisements by using the user's actions, gender and access history, etc. within this service.
  8. For other purposes that this company explains to users when collecting personal information from said users.
  9. To execute its rights and/or obligations based on these terms and/or applicable laws.
  10. For after-service and inquiries

### About the Sharing and Use Limitation of Personal Information

Except in the cases set forth below, this company shall not use/share personal information beyond the extent required to accomplish the purpose of use without getting the prior consent of the users themselves.

  1. When it is permitted by law.
  2. When the users consent.
  3. When responding to a complaint that someone's posting or content violates another's right.
  4. When this company provides personal information to a service provider which is selected through a prescribed procedure to assist this company's operation for the purpose of detecting/preventing acts which may be potentially illegal, and to implement joint services.
  5. When it is necessary to protect someone's life, physical body or property, and it is also difficult to obtain the consent of the user.
  6. When it is necessary to disclose the information to a credit card company, an agent to conduct credit card settlement, a financial institution and/or a collection agent in order to settle the usage fee of a credit card of a user.
  7. When this company believes it is necessary and discloses information to a court, a prosecutor's office, a police office, a tax office and/or a bar association, or to an institution which has an equivalent authority, which owes to this company a confidentiality obligation.
  8. In the case that this company merges, transfers its business or for other reasons transfers its business operations, when this company discloses information to the acquirer of the business.

### About the Safety Administration of the Personal Information

  1. This company will supervise the administration of the personal information appropriately to prevent any leak and/or damage of the personal information and to make sure the security of the personal information shall be maintained.
  2. Only authorized persons of this company shall handle the personal information, and only the extent necessary to execution their functions.
  3. When this company outsources the handling of the personal information, this company shall execute a confidentiality agreement and supervise the delegated agent.

### About the Administration of Personal Information outside of this Service

This company bears no responsibility for the use of personal information collected on Websites linked from this service, such as third party sites, or services which can be accessed via this service. Therefore, this company assumes neither the obligation nor the responsibility as to the regulations and activities of these enterprises or sites. Please confirm the privacy policies of each such site.

### About the History Information and Characteristic Information

This company acquires information, such as the functions and the services that the users used in this service, the content of postings, information used for communications between users, the history of browsed pages and advertisements, the time zone of the usages, the method of use, the use environment (including various settings information for the usage), the user's IP address, cookie information, location information, and terminal identification information, when the users use this company's or our business partners' (hereinafter referred to as "business partners") (including the source of information, advertisement sponsors, and advertisement recipients) services or browse pages thereof.

### Purpose of the Use of the History Information and Characteristic Information

This company uses the history information and characteristic information for the following main purposes:

  1. To check if the access is by the same user or not.
  2. To prompt a user to re-log in after a certain time has lapsed in order to protect the security of the user.
  3. To survey the number of users of this service or the sites of the business partners for which this company distributes advertisements, or to survey the number of users introduced to this service or to the sites of the business partners.
  4. In order for this company or the business partners to distribute and/or provide the most suitable content, advertisements and various services for the customers.
  5. To analyze/extract data in order to enhance and improve this service and the advertisement content that this company or the business partners provide, or to examine a new service.
  6. When this company analyzes data and provides information, to advise the business partners about what kind of advertisements, information and services will be effective for them to post or provide.
  7. When this company needs to check the service usage status of a customer to respond to an inquiry from the customer.

### About Security

This company uses multiple tools (encryption, passwords, physical security method, etc.) to protect users from unjust access or leakage of the personal information, and adopts a strict security standard. However, please note that this company cannot make any guarantee concerning security.

### Disclaimer of Liability

In the following cases, this company shall not be liable for the acquisition of the personal information by a third party.

  1. When a user himself/herself reveals his/her personal information to other users using a function of this service or by other means.
  2. When a user becomes identifiable by chance through his/her activity information or by the information another user inputs.
  3. When a user, other than the owner of the personal information, acquires information identifying a specific individual (ID, password, etc.).

### About Access, Disclosure, Correction, Deletion, and Suspension, etc.

This company shall handle the disclosure, correction, addition, deletion, suspension of usage, erasure, stoppage of third party disclosure and demand for notice of use purpose in accordance with the Personal Information Protection Law and other applicable laws. Users may confirm, correct or delete his/her personal information by logging onto this service. If a user wishes to disclose the personal information which this company possesses but does not display in this service, or if the user wishes to make a correction, addition or deletion of the user's personal information which this company possesses, or wishes to stop using the service, then please contact our customer support. In the case that a request is made by a user whose identification is not possible, or the request does not meet the conditions set forth in the Personal Information Protection Law, there may be cases where this company may not be able to accommodate your wishes. Your request may incur a fee, but it will not exceed the amount permissible by law. Personal information which becomes unnecessary for the above stated purposes shall be deleted at the discretion of this company. In principle, this company shall not disclose personal information other than the access log, etc.

### About the Update of the Privacy Policy

This company may revise this Privacy Policy in accordance with a change in laws or as a need arises to protect personal information. In that case, the latest Privacy Policy shall be posted on this service. Please check this page as you use this service and understand the Private Policy of this service.

### Inquiries concerning Privacy Policy

Please contact the following to make an inquiry concerning this company's Privacy Policy.

Supplementary provision  
Enacted on November 11, 2011

Zawatt Inc., PIC of the Personal Information Management  
VOYAGE Share Office BOAT, Shibuya First Place 8F  
8-16 Shinsencho, Shibuya, Tokyo 150-0045
